Night:

ON OFF

Spoilers:

ON HIDDEN

Night: ON OFF

Spoilers: ON HIDDEN

Privacy Policy
==============

_Last updated November 2021_

This document is our privacy policy which describes what information we collect and what it's used for. Your use of the site constitutes your agreement to our policy.

The Information We Collect
--------------------------

During registration, we collect the following information:

* Username
* OpenID/OAuth Identifier
* IP Address

Your username is used as an identifier when posting content to the website. Your OpenID/OAuth identity and IP address will not be shared with any other party, and are collected for the purposes of authentication and abuse prevention.

Use of Cookies
--------------

We use cookies to store persistent login information and save certain user-selected settings and preferences. You can opt to disable cookies from your web browsers privacy settings, but doing so will prevent you from staying logged in between browser sessions.

California Residents
--------------------

The CCPA provides California residents with specific rights regarding their personal information:

* The right to know which personal information is being collected
* The right to know if personal data is being sold or shared, and to whom
* The right to object to the sale of personal data
* The right to access one's own personal information
* The right to equal service and price, even for consumers who exercise their privacy rights

To exercise these rights, please contact us through the methods listed below.

How To Contact Us
-----------------

Should you have other questions or concerns about this policy, please send us an email via the "Contact" link at the footer of the page.

•

•

•

Find us on:
